[Music]
I'm rames shvi and I'm a life insurance
adviser with ad Sun Life insurance for
the last 22 years a person who wants to
take this profession very seriously he
needs to have a commitment to serve the
society he need to have that commitment
to uh have a longevity in the uh uh
business we have that uh M program where
uh you know people will be uh educated
how you can take the business to the
next level so that is one of the best
programs I have seen across the industry
for me personally uh I feel you know co
uh thought as a big lesson and during
covid uh two of my customers uh I know
scum to co and
fortunately I had insured them
adequately today their families are
financially secure they don't have any
financial trouble like many of them who
are not insured and confidence they G it
gave me to take it forward and reach out
to more people and the second is uh a
you know a qualification called uh mdrt
I qualified for a couple of times and
that recognition worldwide when we meet
the customers they recognize okay he is
a quality adviser and we need to sit and
discuss with him so that is one very
powerful uh tool that anyone who joins a
new business in into this business they
need to have that goal of uh you know
reaching MD in the first year so if you
uh qualify for MDT you are sure you will
continue this business forever that is
one thing which in my last uh 22 years
have learned you have to be continuously
learning and uh you have to qualify for
the international uh recognition that is
mdrt cot to not many companies have this
program and uh I'm really privileged to
be part of AD Capital ad Sun Life
[Music]